EDOARDO DEBENEDETTI

Computer Science M.Sc. Student @ EPFL

aithub.com/dedeswim +41 76 208 2434 edoardodebenedetti.me

edoardo.m.debenedetti@gmail.com in /in/edoardo-debenedetti

EPFL (Federal Institute of Technology Lausanne) M.Sc. student in Computer Science with a strong focus on Machine Learning and Security. Highly proactive, and curiosity-driven with the goal of becoming an ML Research Scientist.

EDUCATION

EPFL - Federal Institute of Technology Lausanne

M.Sc. in Computer Science | 09/2019 - 07/2021 (expected) Lausanne (Switzerland)

- Focus on Machine Learning and Security.
- GPA 5.63/6.
- Working on a research project with Prof. Troncoso at SPRING Lab on deepfakes counteraction.

PoliTo - Turin Polytechnic University

B.Sc. in Computer Engineering | 09/2016 - 07/2019 Turin (Italy)

- GPA 28.4/30.
- **Graduation mark 110/110**, top 9%, final year GPA 29.8/30.
- Exchange year at 同济大学 (Tongji University), in Shanghai (China), during my entire sophomore year.

Navy Military College "F. Morosini"

High School Diploma | 09/2013 - 07/2016 Venice (Italy)

- Lead sophomores as prefect during my final year.
- Military training on Italian Navy's Ships and at Italian Navy's Marine Corps.

EXPERIENCE

JEToP - PoliTo's Junior Enterprise

International Manager | 10/2018 - 06/2019 Turin (Italy)

Executive Board member responsible for public relations and partnerships.

- While I was in charge, JEToP signed 8 new strategic partnerships.
- Past positions: IT Consultant, Fundraising & Partnership Assistant.

Reply

Software Engineering Intern | 11/2018 - 03/2019 Turin (Italy)

Reply is one of the top IT consulting groups in Italy, with revenue worth €1B+ in 2018.

- Created a chatbot that answers questions about GDPR law.
- Worked on RPA, using Automation Anywhere and Python. One of the bots I created decreased the duration of a task by 88%, without requiring human intervention in it.

PROJECTS

GDPR Chatbot

Reply | 02/2019

A chatbot that answers questions about GDPR, the new European Privacy Law, developed as proof of concept.

- The bot could help 320M+ EU citizens to easily understand GDPR.
- Stack: Telegram, TypeScript on Node.js, Redis, MongoDB, IBM Watson Assistant, Docker.

Subspace Attack Reproduction

EPFL | Fall 2019 | link

Attempt to reproduce the results of the NeurIPS 2019 paper "Subspace Attack: Exploiting Promising Subspaces for Query-Efficient Black-box Attacks", done as a main project for the Machine Learning class.

- With our implementation we reduced by 76% the median attack complexity.
- Obtained grade: 98/100.
- Stack: Python with PyTorch.

AWARDS

PoliTong Scholarship

Turin Polytechnic University & Tongji University Shanghai

Awarded to 11 out of 35 students that participated in the selection. Full scholarship for the **one-year exchange** in Shanghai.

本 LANGUAGES

Italian

Native

English

TOEFL iBT 108/120

French Intermediate

